It's a historic day in global diplomacy.
Any moment now, inside the White House,
newly elected Russian
President Nikolai Kasparov
is expected to sign a landmark accord,
signaling a dramatic shift
from the isolationist era
of his predecessor, Ilya Aminoff.
[applause]
Thank you, President Kasparov.
Ladies and gentlemen,
these trade agreements
and peace accord that
President Kasparov and I
have just signed
are the first step to inviting
Russia back to the table.
They signify the commitment
of our great countries
to shape a mutually beneficial future,
to work hand in hand, to lead by example
towards a common goal
of global peace for all.
This will set the foundation
for future generations of the world.
To feel safe.
To...
[grunts]
-Madame President?
-Cat?
Mom.
Hey, let me in.
Starlight is down.
Evacuate the press now.
I say again, Starlight is down.
Lock down the perimeter. Nobody in our out.
Kasparov and his team
are sfe, no shots fired.
What happened?
I think she's having a heart attack.
Madam president, we need
to get you to the hospital.
I need you to get up, okay?
Reyes, on three. Lets get her up.
One, two, three.
Liberal candidate Nikolai
Kasparov has narrowly
secured the Russian presidency,
heralding in a new day for Russia,
free of the iron grip of
former President Ilya Aminoff,
whose policies have been
called out by world leaders
as the reason for so much
destabilization in the region.
Inaugural festivities are planned for
the next two days at the Kremlin
to celebrate this historic moment.
Kasparov will then travel to
the United States next month,
where he and U.S.
President Catherine Collins
will sign several trade pacts
along with a peace accord
laying the groundwork
for a new age of fellowship
and hope for U.S.-Russian
and global relations.
[gunshot]
I didn't see. What happened out there?
She collapsed during her speech.
We caught her just
before she hit the ground.
That's good, that's good.
Bradycardia, irregular
pulse, equal breath sounds.
78 over 40, run fluids.
President's going to be fine, Miss Collins.
Guardian, Stagecoach en route to lodge.
ETA 30 minutes with early
morning traffic, we'll advise.
[shrieks]
She's in heart block, third degree.
No, no, no, she has a pacemaker.
[coughing]
Okay, back in regular sinus.
Madam President?
Where...
What's going on?
Call Amelia. Call Amelia.
Madam President, Amelia is fine.
She's following us to the hospital.
What happened?
Your pacemaker malfunctioned,
Madam President, and you passed out.
Had I at least signed the accord?
Yes, ma'am. You most definitely did.
That's a relief.
That's not going to be a good look
fainting on national television.
Don't worry about it.
[phone rings]
Where's my phone?
Got it here. Here, hold on.
Might be Amelia.
It's an unknown number.
This is an encrypted line.
It's a message that says,
"We control your pacemaker.
"The United States must
immediately renounce
"and withdraw its support of Kasparov.
"Should you refuse, we
will launch a nuclear weapon
"at the Kremlin.
You have 12 hours to comply."
Are they serious? Is this a joke?
Go on, read it.
I don't think this is a
joke, Madam President.
Any attempt to alter
your pacemaker, you die.
Can they do that? Can
they hack into a pacemaker?
The new ones do have Wi-Fi access.
Some doctors use it to log in remotely
and adjust things on the way to the ER.
Can they use data or
anything else besides Wi-Fi?
No, these devices only
connect to a Wi-Fi connection.
"Any attempt to alter
your pacemaker, you die.
"To show how serious we are,
"we will attack your pacemaker again
so you will be certain
of who is in control."
[screams]
-Madam President.
-She's in heart block.
[groaning]
Hold on.
[coughing]
She's back in regular sinus.
You're going to be all
right, Madam President.
[phone chimes]
"The countdown begins now.
"Every two hours, you
will receive another attack.
"Each time we up the
intensity of our wrath.
"Every time you will come closer to death
"until you do as you've been told.
Renounce Kasparov."
Two hours.
Madam President?
We've got to get that pacemaker out ASAP.
Stagecoach, this is Tracer.
We've got traffic up ahead.
All lanes are closed at DuPont Circle.
We're going to need to
divert to side streets. Over.
Call me that, Tracer. Stand by.
I know you won't like this,
but this is going to get us there faster.
Is that a Meraglim?
Yes, ma'am.
Intelligence is banned in America.
I should now. I banned it.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Madam President,
but I need you to stop talking.
You need to rest and get your vitals up.
Tracer. Stagecoach.
Stagecoach, go ahead.
Divert to 20th.
The protocol is 22nd.
I'm in DOT's ops, let me handle it.
Stagecoach, I know you're in charge,
but I would advise against it.
You're going to get an Alpha Charlie
if you deviate from procedure.
-I will as well.
-This will be on me.
This is the President's life.
Hang a right on 20th. Do it now.
Roger that.
Hang on.
[tires squeal]
Oh!
I've got control of the traffic lights.
We'll be there in less than five minutes.
Mom? Is she okay?
She's stable, Miss Collins.
You're welcome to follow us,
but we'll need to get her situated.
We lost Dad to cancer less than a year ago.
I'm not ready to lose her, too.
Amelia, I promise you
we're going to solve this
and figure out who's behind
the messages in the text.
I'm going to hold onto your
mom's phone for a while.
Thanks, Jake.
Agent Pike.
I have confirmed that
this room is Wi-Fi free.
A room? Couldn't you get a whole wing?
I can't do the wing just yet.
Doctors and patients need Wi-Fi.
A move that big is going
to take some coordination,
but they will start moving
patients out to fully secure.
All right, Agents, I'm going.
Copy that, Miss Collins.
We'll reconvene later.
How are you feeling, Mom?
Like I've been hit by a Mack truck.
I'm going to be fine.
I can't survive another loss like Dad's.
Shh.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay...
Okay.
All right, you stay with the president.
I need to update Goddard
on everything that's transpired.
I'm going to have Mr. Marcus
bring me the IMSI-catcher.
See if we can run a diagnostic and isolate
the origin of these texts.
Also, I'm going to scan
the president's phone
and see if we can figure out
who's behind the hacking of the pacemaker
and see if this nuclear
threat is viable or not.
-I want the best doctor now.
-Yes, sir.
Everyone on the team
is praying for her, sir.
Thank you.
Here comes Goddard. He looks pissed.
Reyes, would you escort the vice president
in the room, please?
Yes, sir. Mr. Vice President?
Pike.
Mr. Goddard, the president's
pacemaker was compromised today.
You know, I got a call from the supervisor
of the Department of Transportation
that there was a traffic
light that was hacked
somewhere around 20th Street.
Do you know anything about that?
Yes, sir. That was me.
I used a Meraglim.
Okay, that's illegal.
Now, I know you were recruited
based on your cracking skills,
but that doesn't give you carte blanche.
Sir, I was doing what I
thought was necessary
to save the president's life.
You put lives at risk.
Now, God forbid there was an accident.
The President's critics
would have had a field day.
Madam President?
This is Dr. Amara Nabulsi
and Nurse Sophia Bell.
Dr. Nabulsi is the
chief of cardiology here.
And we attempted to reach out to Dr. Walsh,
the doctor that originally
put in your pacemaker,
but his office said he was
out of the country on vacation.
They're still trying to reach him now.
Thank you for coming, Doctor.
I wish the circumstances were different,
but I don't want you to worry.
We're going to take good care of you.
Please, let's get this
damn thing out of me.
That is the plan, Madam President.
We have a replacement en route as we speak,
one that cannot be hacked,
no Wi-Fi access, just old school,
hands-on access only.
Wonderful, thank you.
Of course. We'll head into
surgery as soon as it arrives.
[door opens]
Jake.
Mr. Marcus.
Kaneko. Sorry to pull you off course.
We can't have criminals
like yourself using this
to disable military drones again.
Thanks for bringing it, sir.
I just got off a call with DHS.
They've been picking up a lot of chatter
from the insurgent group,
the Patriot Command,
especially in the last couple of hours.
Interpol has nothing outstanding,
but the FBI has drummed
up some solid intel.
Patriot Command.
They've been on my
radar for quite some time.
They have financial ties to Russia.
They run deep.
And they've also been extremely vocal about
their disdain for President Collins.
Yeah, but would these
guys have access to a nuke?
Chances are slim, but they've been dealing
with a lot of bad insurgents probably.
Would they have the ability
to hack a pacemaker, too?
Navi-Pace.
The manufacturer that makes
the President's pacemaker.
It would require an access
code for each pacemaker.
So it wouldn't be too hard to hack into
a Wi-Fi-enabled pacemaker
if you had that code.
So then who has access to those codes?
Navi-Pace employees, medical staff?
It's a good place to start.
Okay, here we go.
The U.S. Securities and Exchange
Commission has been tracking
investments made by the Patriot
Command and their affiliates.
They purchased land and other hard assets
using mostly shell corporations.
If they're Russian funded,
this could be a way
around the current sanctions.
And they also have correspondence
with Alexei Serov.
I know that name.
He's just on about
everybody's terrorist watch list.
Basically rogue tribal
warlord operating around
the Sunni region in Russia
near the Ukraine border.
He's reputed to have
access to a nuclear weapon
through his connection with North Korea,
but this isn't verified.
That's great, but how
does this all tie together?
Because the SEC lists
attempts by the Patriot Command
to buy large stock holdings
of random medical companies
including property of a
pacemaker manufacturer,
Navi-Pace.
That's the connection.
We need to get down there and
we need to see what we can find.
Navi-Pace is based out of New Orleans.
The Patriot Command known to have
a training facility there, too.
All right, now we got something.
Pike, I want you to bring
all this to Mr. Goddard.
Tell them that we need to
send a team there ASAP.
Yes, sir.
I'll have the IMSI running.
If it picks up anything
unusual, let me know.
Yeah, of course.
Oh, shit. Let me check on the president.
She should be getting out of surgery.
[heart monitor beeping]
I'm getting the doctor.
Dr. Nabulsi, somebody!
[groans]
She's having another attack!
Madam president, breathe. Breathe.
Okay, the numbers are coming down.
Okay.
She's stabilizing.
[sighs]
Doctor, we're in a secured room
and the president was still attacked?
Why haven't you removed
the president's pacemaker yet?
We're still waiting on a replacement.
Hospitals don't keep older
model pacemakers on hand
and that's what we need
to prevent the president
from future attacks.
It should arrive any minute.
Well, you can take this
one out in the meantime.
Look, I understand your concern,
but given the president's
history of cardiomyopathy,
I don't want to risk removing the pacemaker
without having one on hand.
Mom, please be okay.
Where's Charles?
I'm here, Cat.
Excuse me.
I signed the document.
Amendment 25, Section 3.
You're in charge.
Don't screw it up.
I won't, Cat.
But you're going to be back in no time.
If I'm not, codes.
I'm gonna be sick.
We must schedule a press conference
regarding my transfer to power.
With all due respect, sir, why?
If President Collins
is no longer in charge,
what's the point of continuing to harm her?
Because they're terrorists, sir.
Whether President Collins
is an acting president or not,
she is still their hostage.
I'll keep your words in
consideration, Agent.
Pike, with me.
Yes, sir.
Keep your emotions in check, Agent.
The president cannot fall under my watch.
Our watch. Okay?
Any new developments?
The Patriot Command is involved here.
We're still digging,
but considering the insurgents involved,
the threat is real.
Okay, elaborate.
We discovered that the Patriot Command
has been using hidden Russian funds
to make several large purchases,
including the warehouse
where Navi-Pace is located.
Na... Isn't that the manufacturer
that makes the president's pacemaker?
Yes, sir, that's correct.
Okay.
Where are we on the nuclear threat?
No leads on that just yet,
but we're still considering
how it ties into the pacemaker.
Okay, I'll call Special Ops.
We've got an assault team
out there to the warehouse.
I'm putting you on point here.
Sir, I'm the president's lead detail.
Why would I be leaving?
Just hear me out. You're good with tech.
The president's pacemaker's being attacked
electronically, remotely.
I need someone well versed in IT out there
in the field, on the team, and that's you.
Take Reyes with you.
I want both of you guys out there.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Are you okay, Ms. Collins?
Yeah, I'm just sick to my
stomach, worried about my mom.
Any other symptoms?
I haven't felt that great
the last couple of mornings,
to be honest.
And is this usually how you feel?
Not usually.
Any fatigue or other unexplained nausea?
I guess last month or so, I...
You know, why don't I do
some quick blood workup?
This'll stay between us.
Okay, yes, thank you.
Morning, pretty lady.
Are you okay?
Did you tell Goddard about us yet?
No, not yet.
He's gonna find out and
you're gonna lose your job.
I'm not gonna lose my job.
-I just got promoted.
-You don't know that.
Look, you moved up to presidential detail
faster than any other agent in the service.
I... I can't jeopardize
all of your hard work
for something that might not even last.
Wow.
Do you really believe that?
What if we just tell your mom?
It doesn't matter what she thinks.
It's about the voters. You know that.
Look...
You worked really hard, and so did my mom.
And I'm not gonna let
either of you throw that away.
Okay, I mean, she's meeting
with the Russian president today,
signing an accord, bringing peace on earth.
I mean...
I'm not telling my mom.
Yeah. You're right.
Yeah, I'm really gonna miss
waking up to you every morning.
I am too.
Go, before you're late.
My mom will kill you if
you're late today of all days,
and her favorite hobby is axe throwing.
Like you said, it's your mom's big day.
Gotta make sure this day goes perfectly.
Yeah.
All right?
Amelia.
What did Dr. Nabulsi have to say?
Just how...
We're talking about how I'm
worried about my mom is all.
Yeah.
Look...
We have a lead.
New Orleans.
[reporters shouting]
Good afternoon.
I'm sure you've heard the news
of President Collins' collapse
at today's historic
peace accord with Russia.
But I'm here to happily report
that she's currently resting
and in stable condition.
And she is receiving expert care.
However, in the meantime,
we've enacted the 25th amendment
to ensure that our great nation
continues to operate smoothly.
I will be acting commander in chief
until President Collins is well
enough to return to her duties.
Thank you very much, and God bless America.
[reporters shouting]
The IMSI catcher didn't
find anything unusual.
Seems whatever they're
using is highly encrypted.
We're just gonna have to dig deeper.
You mind if we take it with us?
I don't think low level
Patriot Command is gonna be
that concerned about
communication like their bosses.
Yeah, go for it. Take it.
Kaneko and I'll stay here and keep working.
-Stay connected. Be safe.
-Thank you, sir.
-One more thing.
-Yeah.
This is the president's phone.
It'll be safer here with you.
I'm certain that the
hackers will be in contact.
Will you let me know when they do?
Yeah, of course.
Thank you, sir.
Not our first rodeo.
Anyone have eyes on Nurse Sophia?
I'll go look for her, sir.
Keep me updated, Marcus.
Nabulsi's looking for you.
They're prepping for
the president's operation.
Lucky you, you found me first.
We'd better make this quick
before they send someone
out looking for you, too.
Mmm.
This place looks deserted.
I thought it was supposed
to be operational.
Yeah, I don't like it.
This doesn't seem right.
Oh, crap.
Call Goddard, run it by him.
I'm on it.
[phone vibrates]
Mr. Goddard.
Yes, sir, we're here, but
it seems to be abandoned.
Doors are locked and
there's a stay-out sign
posted by the Louisiana Department
of Public Safety and Corrections.
All right, let me put a call in.
How long is that going to take, sir?
I'm going to make the call. You stand by.
What did he say?
He's going to try to get us clearance.
He said to stand by.
We don't have time to wait.
What are you thinking, Pike?
Pike, Pike, come on, look.
You know, I'm gonna start
calling you AC for Alpha Charlie
because you love getting your ass chewed.
We're at war, Reese. Can't just sit around.
We need answers.
Strange.
It's already unlocked.
It is.
I got your six.
Might have a real threat inside.
Watch your corners.
After you.
Yeah, they're definitely
moving stuff in and out of here.
Yeah, something's going on.
Clear.
All right, look.
We need to do a proper
sweep of the building.
We need to find anything
that can tie this to the Patriot command
or the Russian insurgents.
Let's see what I can find in the office.
I'll cover you.
Reyes.
Patriot Command.
The name of the surgeon
that put in Starlight's
pacemaker six months ago
was Steven Walsh, right?
Yeah, sounds familiar.
All right, let's move.
All right, let's finish our sweep.
Looking for anything that
ties to Patriot Command.
Okay.
[whispering]
[gunshot]
Man down! Man down!
Move.
I got you, buddy. I got you.
Meryl's down! Meryl's down!
Up top.
Hang in there, buddy. Hang in there.
[gunfire]
[grunts]
Ah!
[gunfire]
Man down! Man down!
He's alive!
Stay down. Don't move.
Don't move.
Federal agents, do not move.
Let me see your hands.
Let's talk.
No! No!
No! No, no, no!
[grunting]
Damn it!
Patriot Command.
Let's get Meryl. Get out of here.
Found Sophia.
She was sourcing some
equipment for the surgery.
She's heading back to Collins now.
-Thanks, Marcus.
-Yeah, you bet.
[phone vibrates]
Pike.
Mr. Goddard, we investigated the warehouse.
After I specifically told you to wait?
They knew we were coming.
The team suffered a casualty.
Who?
Meryl, our sharpshooter.
God damn it. I told you to stand by
and wait for local law enforcement.
Then you'd have backup
to provide a perimeter.
We couldn't wait, sir.
They knew we were coming.
Did you find anything?
Did you find anything, agent?
Yes.
Looks like something large
was moved out of here recently.
There was Patriot propaganda everywhere.
All the deceased gunmen had their patches.
I also found a shipping confirmation
to the house of Dr. Stephen Walsh.
The surgeon that installed
Starlight's pacemaker.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll send Marcus
and Kaneko to check it out.
Anything on the nuke?
Nothing on that front yet, sir.
But like I said, something large
was moved out of here recently.
Maybe a dirty bomb?
Perhaps.
Look, Pike...
you can't be disobeying
instructions in the field.
I'm putting Reyes in charge of the team.
I understand, sir.
Put him on.
-But, sir...
-What?
Is there a sit-rep on Starlight?
She's going into surgery in 10 minutes.
Put Reyes on.
Goddard.
Sir.
Reyes, you're in charge now.
Stand by until you hear back from me.
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
-Marcus.
-Yeah?
I need you to go over to
Dr. Stephen Walsh's office immediately.
Kaneko, you go with
him, okay? Check it out.
-Of course.
-Got it.
Here's the president's phone, sir.
Yep.
Stay frosty out there.
You bet.
Love you, Mom.
I love you, too.
You're going to do great.
Amelia, can I speak with you?
Yeah.
I need to prep in for
your mother's surgery,
but I wanted to let you know
that your blood work came in.
And?
You're pregnant.
[sighs]
Okay.
Oh...
We're going to give you a local
anesthetic, Madam President.
You're going to feel a bit lightheaded.
Just get this thing out of me.
Then let that go to work.
You're going to feel like you're
asleep or in a dreamlike state,
but you won't be totally out of it.
Yes, I remember.
Are we ready, nurse?
-Yes, doctor.
-The patient is sedated?
The pacemaker is prepared.
We're just shy of an hour
before the threat of the next shock.
We'll barely make it.
Scalpel.
[alarm sounds]
She's flat lining.
Get the oxygen on.
[phone chimes]
Oh, shit.
170. This is it.
Let's go.
That's odd.
We're definitely not the first ones here.
Not by a long shot.
Dr. Walsh, federal agents.
Hello? Anybody here?
Shh.
Clear.
Is this him?
Yeah. He's been dead a while.
Holy...
What's this guy been up to?
I thought this guy was out
of the country on vacation.
I'm going to call for the coroner
and update Pike and Goddard.
Think you can get in?
Give me two minutes.
Pike, it's Marcus.
-Hello, sir.
-Hang tight.
I'm going to loop you into Mr. Goddard.
Well, I don't think that's
such a good idea, sir.
Goddard.
It's Marcus, sir. Found Dr. Walsh.
He's dead.
What?
Strangled, most likely.
Are you sure it's him?
Yes, sir. I recognize him.
How is she?
All right, we have her stabilized.
We have to get that thing out of her.
You saw the text.
So my mother is just
supposed to die either way?
Amelia, please. She's not going to die.
I promise.
How can you promise that
when nobody can keep her safe?
Pike: What's going on, sir?
Chaos happening.
Okay, listen, Pike,
why are you on this call?
I looped him in, sir.
Is everything okay over there?
Starlight, she just got another shock.
This one practically flat lined her.
I mean, they knew she was being wheeled in
to remove the pacemaker.
Did you find anything at Dr. Walsh's?
Yeah, we did.
This guy has a complex server set up here.
Why does a cardiologist
need all that equipment?
That's how they're doing it.
What do you mean?
We discussed someone from Navi-Pace
retaining access to
President Collins' pacemaker.
It's been her original
surgeon this whole time.
But if Walsh is dead, that
means that someone else also
might have access codes to that.
We'll likely know more once
Kaneko hacks the server.
Okay, I'll bring the farm in on this.
Do a deep dive on Dr. Walsh's history.
Triple check everybody on this team.
We only have about eight hours left.
I need answers on that nuke.
-Yes, sir.
How is Starlight, sir?
They're weighing their options now.
May I suggest moving
her to a CT or X-ray room?
That should block out any
outside electronic interference.
I'll mention it.
How you doing, man?
Almost there.
And boom, cracked the server.
Kaneko's into the server.
I'll wait.
You're on speaker. Go ahead.
Aside from several deposits
from an offshore account,
Walsh was using a Tor network.
It's more encrypted than a
VPN, but not enough for me.
Walsh was able to ping
Starlight's pacemaker
from his home.
That's why he's been able to attack her,
even though he's dead.
No, not exactly.
The doctor's setup here was just a relay.
The Tor's ISP is actually
located in Las Vegas.
So we would go to Vegas,
we'd stop the connection,
and we find out who's behind this.
I'll ping you the target locations.
Let's Oscar Mike.
You almost done? We've
got to get out of here.
Let's just take this to the Hoover Building
so I can work on it in the lab.
All right, I'm going to call forensics
and see what their ETA is.
Could it be something besides the Wi-Fi?
Can they control the data
going to the pacemaker?
No, these devices are built
for Wi-Fi connections only.
Agent Pike made a good decision
to move the president to CT.
Those rooms are lined with lead,
so they'll likely block the signals.
We should be safe there.
Should isn't good enough.
My mother needs to be
as protected as possible.
That's why we're moving her, Ms. Collins.
[whispers] On me.
Move!
[shouting]
[gunfire]
Move! Move! On the ground!
I've got two rabbiting up the
stairs, I'm going after them!
Go, I'll cover you!
[gunfire]
[grunting]
Ugh!
[cracks]
Freeze right there, fella.
Let's have a little talk with
your friends downstairs.
Drop your weapon!
Drop it.
You're in no position to negotiate.
Drop the weapon.
You drop your weapon, or
I'm blowing his brains out.
That's right.
Atta-boy.
Now let's go.
Ah!
Don't you move.
Get up.
Let's go.
Why is the secret service here anyway?
We don't run counterfeit.
That it downstairs?
All signs point to yes.
What do you pigs care
about our TOR network?
You tried to kill federal officers.
What we want with your network
really doesn't matter now, does it?
It's not like you identified yourselves.
Just shut up.
-Weeks.
-Come on, man.
Who are you working with?
I don't know what you're talking about.
We run an online betting site.
All legal.
You are Patriot Command.
In bed with the Russians.
Then why waste your breath asking me?
To test your trustworthiness.
So far you're betting zero.
So happy to disappoint you.
I'm going to give you another chance.
What do you know about the nukes?
[laughs]
Like a nuclear bomb?
Why didn't you ask? It's
right down in the garage.
I mean, how'd you miss it?
Okay.
Look, we just get paid money
to keep the network running.
We keep trespassers off the property.
They don't tell us anything.
I don't know what they're
running on the server.
And I don't know anything about any nuke.
Something else is going on here.
We need to have another look around.
-Yeah.
-Sounds good.
It's not going to matter.
[chuckles]
[beeps]
What did you do?
It's a detonator.
Get him. Let's go. Move!
Get out of here, come on!
We got to move. Let's go.
Come on. Move!
Damn.
All right.
Are you ready, Madam President?
Yes.
Please, let's get this over with.
Let's get her prepped.
She's going to be okay.
[phone vibrates]
What is it?
All right, we're going to
get the anesthesia flowing,
some oxygen flowing.
You're going to be great.
[beeping]
Madam President?
Oh!
She's defibbing.
Get her into magnet mode now.
STAT.
Hold on.
She's stabilizing.
Breathe. Relax.
Mom? Mom, are you okay?
What? You can't be in here.
You just said that she was safe in here.
Sir.
They shouldn't have access
to her pacemaker anymore.
You need to calm down.
I...
I... if I don't make it...
No, no, no, no, no.
Mom, don't even dare
say anything like that, okay?
I love you.
Hey! Hey, you're going
to make it through, okay?
You got this. You're strong.
How much more of this can her heart take?
Not much more, I'm afraid.
Isn't there anywhere
in this entire hospital
that doesn't have Wi-Fi?
I don't think it's the Wi-Fi.
[gasps]
[coughs]
[coughing]
It's for a job well done.
Until I need your services again.
[speaks Russian]
[speaks Russian] my friend.
And farewell.
You do realize that your life
means nothing to the
Russians, and clearly not yourself.
So if you want any
semblance of a life left,
you better cooperate.
Now, what do you know about the nuke?
Look, I already told you.
I don't know anything
about any nuclear bomb.
I want to speak to my lawyer.
Now.
Let's go. Out.
Yeah, watch it.
Let's go.
Was President Collins attacked again?
Yeah. Get Reyes on the phone.
[phone rings]
-Have a nice trip.
Reyes?
It's Marcus and Mr. Goddard on speaker.
Go.
Reyes.
I thought you took care of that, Agent.
Not quite, sir.
Coleman sent off C-4
and flattened the house.
Why?
Well, we moved Starlight to the CT room.
She was still attacked.
Agent.
Sir. Pike.
If these attacks keep happening,
it can't be Wi-Fi enabled.
Walsh must have preloaded
Starlight's pacemaker
with some additional access codes.
Where does that leave us, then, Agent?
Well, the only place there
wouldn't be interference
would be aboard Angel.
You want us to move the
President onto Air Force One?
Yes, sir.
It's shielded for all
types of electrical signals
once it's in the air.
We all know that that's the
safest plane on the planet.
We'll take that into consideration then.
I hesitate to even ask about the nuke.
Batting zero on that, sir.
The Patriot Command leader here says
that they were just paid
to protect the server.
And you believe him?
Yes, sir, I do.
All right.
Stand by until you hear
back from me, okay, Agent?
Roger that.
Every time Pike makes a recommendation,
Starlight still gets shocked.
What are you saying, sir?
Don't you find that odd?
Sir, he's a good agent.
Yeah, I know.
Let's get Air Force One ready.
Copy that, sir.
It's Marcus.
Text from Kaneko.
It says Walsh's TOR network is being pinged
from a cell phone
triangulated to the Mint Casino.
Let's move.
We should be there in 10 minutes.
Once we get that cell phone,
you can patch it into Kaneko.
That could hold the answer to everything:
The pacemaker, the nuke, all of it.
[phone rings]
Yes, sir.
Agent Reyes.
I understand you're en
route to the Mint Casino
to investigate a possible
server connection.
Yes, sir, Kaneko messaged Agent Pike.
Yeah, I want Pike back on the plane to D.C.
I... I'm sorry, sir, can
you say that again?
I said I want Agent Pike back in D.C.
If he's not back in D.C. as instructed,
both of your careers are toast.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir, I'll see that he gets there.
Advise me once you're at the Casino.
What's wrong?
Goddard wants you back
in D.C. or we're both done.
What?
What did he say?
Didn't give a reason.
Shit, Jake, this makes no sense.
I mean, you're the IT guru, not me.
We need you.
So what?
You're gonna physically
force me to get on that plane?
Come on, man.
My hands are tied.
All right, look, we'll go to the Casino
and I'll get back to D.C.
Yeah.
Please, keep your eyes on the road.
Yes, sir.
So how are we going to play this?
Well, it's not going to play
very well with three
commandos running into a casino.
I'll fly solo.
Bring Kaneko into comms?
Yep, Roger that.
-Jacket?
-There you go, buddy.
You want this?
All right, Kaneko's linked in.
Kaneko: Hey, Pike, I've hacked
into the hotel security system.
I have access to all their codes,
room keys, and room safes.
I'm going to text you the bypass code
for the freight elevator.
Get you up there without interruption.
The cell phone is in a master bedroom safe
in the presidential
suite on the 11th floor.
Kaneko, I'm going in.
We got company.
[grunting]
[panting]
[shrieks]
[grunting]
[gunshot]
Kaneko, going into the safe.
Left side of the bed.
Safe code is 1970.
I got it.
Come on, guys.
Is that it?
Kaneko?
I'm here.
I'm wiring you access
to the Mint Casino phone
over the IMSI-catcher.
Copy that.
Sent.
And received.
I'm going to need a few
minutes to sort through the data.
Copy that.
We'll wait to hear back from you.
I guess take me back to Nellis.
Go back to D.C.
We'll be taking off fairly soon, ma'am.
And as soon as we're up in the air,
we're going to start immediately
preparing for your surgery.
As soon as I get the go
ahead from Dr. Nabulsi,
I'll notify ATC that will be dark
for the duration of the procedure,
which I'm told is roughly an hour.
Yes, Mr. Goddard, provided
there are no more surprises.
Thank you, agent.
I want this plane up
in the air immediately.
No delays.
Air traffic control, this is Air Force One
preparing for takeoff.
Ladies and gentlemen, we
have received our clearance.
Please buckle your seat
belt. Sit back and relax.
We'll have you in the air in just a moment.
Mr. President, everyone on
board has been triple vetted, sir.
Thank you, Agent Goddard.
Would you mind if I spoke freely, sir?
Sure.
Sir, I really feel we're taking a
chance with you on board here.
You have family, correct, Agent Goddard?
Yes, sir. I have a wife and two children.
And if one of them are having surgery,
you want to be with them, right?
Yes, sir.
Well, Catherine is my family.
She's like my sister.
So I'm going to be here to
support her all the way through.
I can do my job just fine from here.
Besides, we're in one the
safest plane in the world.
We'll be fine.
[phone rings]
[phone vibrates]
Amelia?
Jake, where are you?
I'm getting ready to head back to D.C.
What's going on there? How's your mom?
They just boarded her on Air
Force One like you suggested.
Good.
She'll finally be safe now.
I wanted to...
In case something happens, I just...
I wanted to tell you that...
[phone vibrates]
Amelia, I'm sorry. I got to take this.
Call me the moment she
gets out of surgery, okay?
Okay, but I...
[sighs]
Pike, I got something.
Let's hear it.
I just broke through.
The data's just encrypted
numbers from two cell numbers.
One coming from Aleksei Serov.
So the nuclear threat is credible?
Well, we shouldn't turn a blind eye.
The SAC's already been notified,
and they're scrambling a
team together in the region.
That's good to hear.
You said there was a second number.
You think it could be
connected to the pacemaker?
Likely yes, but that's one
I'm having a hard time with.
And due to time constraints,
I think we should just try calling it.
Whoever's cell it is, it
won't answer a random call.
Can you misdirect it,
make it seem like it's from
the encrypted network?
Piece of cake.
That's why they...
Pay you the crap wages.
I'll conference you in.
I don't know what's on the other line,
so we got to keep this
short so they don't ping it.
Copy that.
Ready?
Put it through.
[phone ringing]
[phone vibrates]
I need to use the
restroom. I'll be right back.
Uh, that's fine.
Looks like they're not answering.
Wait, wait. Just give
it a few more seconds.
Who is this?
[phone chimes]
There's a false alert. I'm checking on it.
Agent Cronin, go check Cabin A.
Who was that?
I don't know.
That voice sounded familiar.
All right, look, it's time for
you to make the big bucks.
I need a name.
I know, I saw.
But who?
That's not what's important right now.
With Vegas compromised and likely Serov,
it's time to move to Plan B.
Hold that thought, give me a second.
Are you good?
Yes.
Are you with me?
Okay, that's my girl.
Huh, the call was routed through
an encrypted phone on Angel,
and it was a woman's voice.
All right, how many women on board?
Hold on.
All right, I got the
passenger list right here.
Their code names, obviously.
Everybody on board has to be on that list.
It's protocol.
Read out the names of the women.
Okay, we got Starlight,
Amelia, and Captain,
but she's the pilot.
I think we can rule her out.
Dr. Nabulsi and Nurse Bell.
But that's it, man.
Are you sure?
100%.
Starlight has been attacked
when Nabulsi was present,
so it has to be that nurse, Sophia.
She's been in close proximity to Starlight
from the get-go.
It's possible she has a radio transmitter
circumventing our security
measures this whole time.
Oh, man.
Kaneko, we can't trust anyone.
I've got to get on that plane.
Well, how are you going to do that?
I don't know. I'll figure it out.
I'll call you back.
It's the nurse?
Affirmative.
I need to get on that plane.
You have a plan?
Just might.
[phone rings]
Kaneko. Yeah, what's the
status of the strike team in Russia?
They took out Serov with a drone, sir.
Preliminary intel shows
that they had an early
Russian SRF missile vehicle
with the low-yield topple.
Could have easily hit
the Kremlin from Sumy.
A strike team is en
route to secure the site.
Good thing we took him out.
Anything else?
Well, has Agent Pike
not contacted you, sir?
Pike? No.
When did you last speak with him?
I just got off the phone with him, sir.
He's heading to Nellis
to try to get on Angel.
We just found out that...
Sir?
[phone rings]
It's Goddard.
Reyes?
Put Pike on the phone now.
You're on speaker, sir.
Goddard, sir.
You are not getting on this plane.
Sir, Angel has been compromised.
I'm coming on board for backup.
The hell you are. You listen.
You're going to make a
ship-to-ship mid-air transfer
and tell everybody on
board that we're on to them.
I will handle things in the air.
You stand down, Agent.
Pull over.
Yeah, this is Special Agent in
charge of Protective Operations
Jim Goddard.
Credential number Romeo-119027.
I've got a rogue agent.
His name is Jacob Pike.
He's headed your way.
I want him stopped,
and I want him detained.
Is that understood?
That is all.
-Good afternoon.
-How's it going?
ID's, please.
How many of you?
Just two of us.
I need you to pop that trunk.
Go for it.
[detector beeping]
All clear.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, gentlemen.
-Good day.
-Have a good one.
Two, three.
Got it.
How much you weigh?
It's all muscle mass.
We'll switch next time.
That was a good call,
anticipating Goddard
would put an alert on you.
Yeah.
Let's get this in the air.
Boys, everything good?
Attention, everyone.
We'll be shutting down all
communications at this time.
We'll have it back up and running
the second the President's
surgery is complete.
ETA, one hour.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Marcus, we're compromised.
I know.
Sorry about this, Jim.
It's nothing personal.
Okay, we're ready to begin.
We need everyone to step out.
Or we could just end it now.
Cat...
If there's another
hiccup, do not resuscitate.
I don't remember you signing a DNR.
Mom...
Don't you want to meet your granddaughter?
Or grandson?
Is it true?
My sweet child.
So I'm really going to need you.
I'll be here for my grandchild.
-Yes, you will.
-And for you.
Let's get this surgery underway.
She's going to be okay now.
Yeah.
I'm just going to go take a moment.
[knocking]
Come in.
Agent Marcus.
Have they started the surgery yet?
All ready, ma'am?
As ready as I'll ever be.
We're going to start with anesthesia.
Ah!
[muffled shouting]
Hey, back the fuck up.
[muffled shout]
What was all that racket?
Dr. Nabulsi's taken care of.
It was you? Both of you.
Keep your voice down.
[sighs] Just text him.
Just text him.
[gasps]
Answer me!
Remember...
Ivan Belsky?
He was one of those you had targeted
by a Ground Branch hit team?
He was my father.
When I saw the
opportunity to help Dr. Walsh
to make America suffer like
it made me suffer, I took it.
We don't sanction assassins.
Liar!
There'll be plenty of time for that later.
Got it.
All right, ETA, two minutes.
Aminoff needs to be reinstated into power.
It's that simple.
Without Russia to keep America in check,
we are on the precipice of World War III.
We thought interrupting your pacemaker
would make you see reason,
but clearly that's not happening.
So good news, we're going
to keep you alive for now,
but... bad news.
I'm going to tell the
pilots to stop circling DC
and we're going to go somewhere remote
and then we're going to launch the nuke.
Unless you denounce Kasparov.
Do you hear me?
I hear you.
[coughs]
Keep that on her.
Mm.
[sighs]
Sorry, about that.
That's the best we can do.
It'll work.
It has to.
All right, so Air Force
One's at 20,000 feet.
I'm going to signal the plane
and try to get her down to 10,000 for you.
Thank you.
Now these magnetic clips will help you
hold onto the other plane.
Now, there's still a possibility
that you could freeze to
death or run out of oxygen.
We don't have a choice.
All right, I'll pull up to her.
Hopefully these guys know Morse code.
What's going on?
What do they want?
Lower. Lower.
Lower.
Any change of heart, Madam President?
I will never back a war criminal.
Do you even know how to use that?
Oh, we have an idea.
Where's President Roberts?
Dead.
And the gold code for
the day is Tango Alpha.
And the destination?
Washington D.C.
Now, all we need is a retinal scan.
And we can do that,
whether you're dead or alive.
Back up. Back up. There.
Open your eyes and look at the monitor.
Open your eyes!
Open her eyes for her.
Capture.
Launch code verified.
Launch sequence activated.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Launch.
Pike, we need to get you on that plane now.
I don't think Goddard waited.
They're signaling SOS back.
Okay.
Listen, they're going to lower the plane.
I told them to get it
to at least 10,000 feet.
They're at 15 now.
All right.
Don't forget to take a deep
breath before you jump.
Hold it as long you can.
You got this, Pike.
[gasps]
Jake?
[shouts]
What?
Open the door!
Clear the door!
Open the door, Amelia!
Opening!
What was that?
I think we're changing altitude.
[groans]
[gasps]
-Amelia!
-Jake!
-Grab my hand!
Oh, you bastard.
My hand!
Pull me in!
Come on! Come on!
What's wrong with you? You're insane!
Unhook me! Unhook me!
Yeah!
He made it!
Get back! Get back!
[grunting]
Marcus, why?
You recruited me!
Haven't you seen the signs, Pike?
America's finished!
You're finished!
[screams]
Good job.
Come on.
-It's Sophia.
-I know.
She's with my mom.
I gotta get this off.
I need you to stay here, okay?
Keep still, Madam President.
You know you're not in charge now.
[gunshot]
-Easy.
-Do not move!
Stay there.
Madam President, are you okay?
They launched a nuclear
missile at D.C., 30 minutes out.
How do we stop it?
You can't.
There has to be a way.
Welcome to World War III.
And remember, you did this.
There's no override codes?
I told you, you...
[groans]
Madam President!
Drop it! Drop it!
Put it down!
Dr. Walsh!
A radio transmitter.
Simple, yes?
Wi-Fi for the first attack,
so we wouldn't have to be too close.
But we knew you would figure that out so...
[gunshot]
Jake.
Thank you very much, Sophia.
That's all we actually needed from you.
By the way, we are avoiding World War III.
Avoiding a war by
launching a nuclear warhead?
There will be some blood
spilled, yes, but no World War.
No one benefits from a war
of that magnitude, Agent Pike.
Help me understand this.
I will oblige, Madam President.
This will make Kasparov seem
like an incompetent president.
Accidental nuclear
launch due to system error.
Kasparov will take the blame.
And with the destruction of D.C., poof,
America will be crippled for a while.
Aminoff will be reinstated.
And I, yours truly,
have been promised a very,
very high position for my efforts.
And by the time America
recovers, if it does,
Mother Russia will once again
be the global dominant power.
With me.
Amelia, why don't you join us?
Amelia, they launched a nuke at D.C.
No... Shh...
Do me a favor, just kindly
move over to the wall, right?
Don't, don't do that.
Don't try anything stupid, okay?
Agent Pike, if the both of you are here,
does that mean that
Marcus is no longer with us?
We threw him off the plane.
[laughing]
You did?
Well, that just actually brought
you your life back, agent.
Because I may need your IT experience
should something go wrong.
Jake!
It's okay, it's alright.
Hey, I didn't hit anything vital.
I just need him
incapacitated for a little while.
[groans]
Shh, you hear that?
Are there any escort fighters out there?
No.
And what about the Doomsday plane
that follows Air Force One?
You all think I'm stupid, right?
Thank God I took care of that.
Amelia, I think I need you to come with me
to make sure nobody else
does any funny business.
And actually you can help me
fly the plane while you're at it.
I've never flown this
model aircraft before.
How about if I put a few
holes in your mother?
Okay, I'll go with you.
Good girl.
Close that football.
Close it!
Thank you.
Pick it up. Let's go.
Go.
Move. Move!
Agent Pike.
Hang on.
[groans]
What are you gonna do?
[grunts]
I don't have an access card.
Madam President, I'm gonna
need you to get off that table.
So this is where the magic happens.
Put the football on the desk.
Put it on the desk!
Open it.
Down on your knees. On your knees!
Hands behind your head.
Madam President, cover your ears.
What was that?
It sounded like an explosion.
Go check it out.
What was that? What was that?
No!
Stop! Stop!
Shut up! What did I tell you?
Bitch!
All right, come on.
Walsh is probably in the control room.
Wait here.
I'm going after him.
-Do not do anything stupid!
-Walsh!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
You are much too slow, Agent Pike.
Isn't that the mother of
your future 100 babies,
if there is a future?
Put the freaking gun down!
Put it down!
All right. I'm putting it down.
Just please, don't hurt her.
I so wanted to put a bullet
right here through her damn skull.
That was really stupid what you just did.
And now I'm just gonna finish you.
For Mother Russia.
Mr. Goddard.
Damn it.
Oh, my God.
Amelia, I need you to do
your best to fly this plane
while the President
and I try to stop the nuke.
Okay?
We need to open up comms again.
You need to get in touch with Vandenberg,
and you need to tell them to
initiate emergency protocols
if they haven't already.
All right? You can do this.
Copy.
You can't stop it, Agent.
All right, Amelia.
Autopilot disengaged.
You're trained for this.
I could try and tie in
the missile's trajectory
into the MDA, see if they can
shoot it down over the ocean.
-Not this one.
-Why not?
This is a Perses Hypersonic MK-11.
It moves too fast and too low
for anything or anyone to shoot it down.
Man: Angel! Vandenberg, you copy?
Go ahead, Vandenberg.
We've been trying to contact you.
Comms were dark for over an hour, Angel.
I know, we're having some problems up here.
The Missile Defense Agency has detected
a nuclear threat fast
approaching the Eastern Shore.
Confirming ETA in five minutes.
Copy, we're aware.
We're working on it from
our end, I'll keep you apprised.
Angel out.
I've got to try something, Madam President.
Where are you going?
Where is it? Where is this thing?
Come on.
I had it here.
Yes.
Agent Pike.
The Meraglim.
I should have thought of this before.
What's that going to do?
Imagine two people trying to communicate
that speak different languages.
Eventually, they just give up.
What exactly are you doing?
I'm writing code.
Code that it won't
understand into the system.
Autopilot engaged.
I put on autopilot away from D.C.,
but I don't know how far it'll get us.
What's going on? How much time do we have?
I can do this.
[alarm sounds]
What is that? What does that alarm mean?
We lost the network signal.
It went down over the Atlantic Ocean.
Does that mean we stopped it?
You did it.
[laughing]
You did it, Agent Pike.
How's she doing?
She's resting.
Amelia, I almost lost you today.
I'm not going to lose you again.
I want us to be together.
And if that means losing
my job, then so be it.
Jake... shh.
Sorry.
If you want to, of course.
But I can't deny what we had
isn't special or great, Amelia.
How stupid you two must think I am.
I'm the President of the United States.
It's my job to know things.
Do you really think you could hide
how you two feel for each other from me?
Are you okay with it?
It depends.
Does he know?
Do I... Do I know about what?
Jake...
I'm pregnant.
You're kidding.
That's great news.
Yeah?
You're going to be a mom.
I'm going to be a dad.
Okay, I don't have a problem.
But I have a request.
No, it's an order.
You get married ASAP before
the press finds out about it.
Such a romantic proposal, Mom.
Hey, what do you say?
Yeah.
-Okay.
-Let's land this plane.
-Yeah.
Almost done.
Gear down.
At least The weather's on our side.
[alarm sounds]
Come on.
The landing gear is shot.
Tower, Air Force One, we have a problem.
Landing gear won't come down.
That's probably Marcus's doing.
Roger, Air Force One,
we're rolling the trucks.
You are clear to land, any runway.
Madam President, I'm
going to need your seat.
Copy, Tower, we're coming in hot.
I'm going to have to
throttle down to pull up.
Okay.
On my mark, we both
pull the yokes together.
We land this together.
If anything happens...
We can't let it.
Right.
-I love you.
Now!
[grunting]
Ah!
I can't, it's too tight.
[alarm sounds]
Come on.
We got it!
-We got it!
[shouting]
[grunts]
[panting]
Are you okay?
Yeah. Are you okay, Mom?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
We did it!
[siren blaring]
Angel landed.
We've got the emergency call in.
They should be here any minute.
Come on.
My grandchild's father
just saved all our asses.
Well done, Jake.
I couldn't have done it without you two.
Are you sure you don't
want to come with us?
I'll catch up with you soon.
I've got to deal with the mess
with the loss of Mr. Goddard and Marcus.
Okay.
I'll see you soon.
[laughing]
Yes, no, it's not that. It's...
Hello, lovely ladies,
how did the surgery go?
Oh, already that comfortable, huh?
I'm sorry, Madam President.
[laughing]
You're among family now.
But out there?
Understood, Madam President.
Since you asked, the
surgery went very well.
My doctor tells me that my
new pacer cannot be hacked.
No Wi-Fi, transmitter,
Bluetooth, airy-fairy,
old-school, hands-on access only.
That's great news.
Did you find out any more
information about Dr. Walsh?
I did.
He's actually Sergey "Vanya" Lebedev,
a former Spetsnaz GRU surgeon,
living in the U.S. for the
last 15 years as Dr. Walsh.
He was promised the
prime minister of Russia
if Aminoff became president again.
Wow.
With the terrorists and
Patriot Command gone,
America is a much safer
place than it was 24 hours ago,
thanks to the two of you.
Well, I've been meaning to ask,
are you sure you're ready for this?
I mean, having children
is a big responsibility.
I think after yesterday,
we're ready for anything.
That's true.
I agree.